Guide to the Cornell Black Alumni Association records,1969-2006.
Cornell Black Alumni Association records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Black Alumni Association records, 1969-2006.
41-6-3683
Cornell Black Alumni Association.
1.3 cubic feet.
Printed Materials, Publications, Photographs
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes minutes of meetings, bylaws, event flyers, publications, membership lists, photo albums from the 1970s, and time capsule.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Founded in 1976, the Cornell Black Alumni Association (CBAA) was conceived as an organization devoted to providing a communcation network for Black alumni. Its current mission is to promote the professional development of Black alumni; to provide opportunities for alumni to "give back" to the Cornell community; to provide support for current Black students through scholarships; and to aid in maintaining the diversity of the student body at Cornell.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes minutes of meetings, bylaws, event flyers, publications, membership lists, photo albums from the 1970s, and time capsule.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Black Alumni Association.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae; Cornell University--Students.
Subjects:
Minority college students--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Minorities--Education, Higher.; African American college students--New York (State)--Ithaca.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
  - Articles, 1969-2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Event Flyers, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - CBAA Events, 1982-1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Questionnaire/Surveys, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Members, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Members, 1979-1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - CBAA/Cornell Reunion Photographs, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - CBAA Reunion Negatives, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CBAA 30th Anniversary Tribute CD, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Unlabeled Photographs (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Financial Documents, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Publications, 1981, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Publications, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Official Documents (Incorporation, By-laws), 1981-1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Official Documents (Correspondence, Proposal), 1982-1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Photo Album, ca. 1970's (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Photo Album, ca. 1970's (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Photo Album, ca. 1970's (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Time Capsule
  - Black Alumni List (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - CBAA Reunion Committee Minutes and Action Items (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 30th Anniversary of CBAA Invitation, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - CBAA Reunion Weekend Fundraisers, 2005 (Box 4)
  - CBAA 30th Anniversary T-shirt, 2006 (Box 4)
  - CBAA Reunion Party Favor, 2006 (Box 4)
  - CBAA Administrator's Award- Mary Mosley, 2006 (Box 4)